const quizArr = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What does Newton's first law of motion cover?",
        options: {
            A: "Gravity",
            B: "Energy",
            C: "Inertia",
            D: "Density",
        },
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which of the following particles is found in the nucleus of an atom?",
        options: {
            A: "Electron",
            B: "Hadron",
            C: "Proton",
            D: "Neutrino",
        },
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is a unit of force called?",
        options: {
            A: "Newton",
            B: "Degree",
            C: "Joule",
            D: "Planck",
        },
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "The amount of matter in an object is called its what?",
        options: {
            A: "Density",
            B: "Weight",
            C: "Mass",
            D: "Cubit",
        },
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which physics law states 'the extension of a spring is proportional to the tension stretching it'?",
        options: {
            A: "Hooke's law",
            B: "Newton's second law",
            C: "Avogadro's law",
            D: "Stefan's law",
        },
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which type of energy is produced through the movements of electrons?",
        options: {
            A: "Electrical",
            B: "Mechanical",
            C: "Thermal",
            D: "Nuclear",
        },
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which of the following is not a form of energy?",
        options: {
            A: "Sound",
            B: "Light",
            C: "Friction",
            D: "Heat",
        },
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What kind of lens does a magnifying glass use?",
        options: {
            A: "Bifocal",
            B: "Convex",
            C: "Concave",
            D: "Trivex",
        },
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which of the following substances allows sound to travel through it at the fastest speed?",
        options: {
            A: "Mercury",
            B: "Helium",
            C: "Steel",
            D: "Water",
        },
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What type of particles did Ernest Rutherford use in his 1911 nuclear theory experiment with gold foil?",
        options: {
            A: "Alpha",
            B: "Beta",
            C: "Delta",
            D: "Gamma",
        },
        answer: "A",
    },
]